Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
The Bulala King
Episode 9
So high
Can we still get the Golden Bulala?
We have endured all the difficulties on the road.
I believe we can get back the Golden Bulala
Let’s go
Is there anyone?
What’s wrong
Did you hear anything just now?
No
Could it be that you are too tired?
Is there anyone?
Who can help me?
let’s go and see
Maybe he really needs help
wait for me
How is it
Have you found the person calling for help?
What a big bird’s nest
You are
Fluffy Little Frost
Fluffy
Little Frost
The only one who knows my baby name is
Father
It’s me It’s me
Fluffy Little Frost
king
The king is okay
Father, I will rescue you right now
I was used as nesting material by that bird.
that bird
Little Frost, quickly get out of the way
No, the giant bird is back
We’ll contain it, save His Majesty
Thank you very much
Little Frost, please be gentle
This nest is still being built and is not strong
sorry sorry
We accidentally made its nest look like this
What should we do now that the giant bird is angry?
We need to repair its nest
This will appease it
Then I’ll help Sparky
let’s go
Sorry, we are repairing your nest.
don’t be angry
It seems more angry
Big bird, look
Please sign for the ultra-luxurious big bird’s nest
Are you okay, Little Frost?
fine
Wolffy, are you okay?
Don’t worry
Let’s go while it’s happy now
Not good, Master Quan
Prince Sparky is missing
Sparky
This is the future king of our Bulala Kingdom
Hate children the most
Uncle
Uncle it is thundering
Aren’t you scared?
can I stay with you
No thanks, Prince Sparky
Go back and rest quickly
Uncle, I want to stay here tonight
please
Uncle
Then you are not allowed to kick the quilt
Uncle, let’s play together
Who let you in? Get out.
sorry
Am I too cruel?
I want to help Uncle sew the embroidery
to apologize to Uncle
That’s not how it’s embroidered
Uncle
Let me teach you
where has he gone
When I collected Bulala
Some people said they saw the prince heading towards the Thorn Forest.
Gather the troops to go to the Thorn Forest
By the way, His Majesty has become like this
but is still alive
It’s really awesome
We Bulala people, as long as the Heart Knot remains,
even if we are scattered, we can survive as long as we can stitch it back together.
So magical
It’s not good, Father’s Heart Knot is too frayed.
Need to be stitched quickly
But there’s still a long way to go back to the city.
Use what’s nearby. There is some Bulala right ahead.
Then let’s go separate ways
Now that we’ve collected everything, let’s start repairing it.
Okay
Bula-bula
You can also do Hulala
What Hulala?
We’re talking about Bulala
This is a blessing to be recited while knitting the body.
Bula-Bula Bulala
Sparky, your knitting skills are amazing.
This is what Uncle taught me.
But why hasn’t His Majesty woke up yet?
Yes, it stands to reason that Father should be awake.
Father, Father, Father
I’m teasing you
Father, it’s great that you’re okay
It’s all thanks to you.
Father, what happened that day?
that day
Be careful everyone
what is
Mon—monster appeared
So scary
Don’t be afraid, everyone
You are afraid
We are good people too
You don’t have to be afraid
Brother, this monster doesn’t seem that dangerous.
We can tell everyone that you don’t have to be afraid anymore
It’s very docile
Brother, save me, brother
That’s how it is
How could this happen? How could Uncle stand by and watch you die?
After all, it happened suddenly
He must be so scared that he was stunned.
Fortunately, Brother is fine too. I’m really lucky.
Just go to the bottom of the cliff and get the Golden Bulala
Everyone no longer has to be afraid of the monster
Let’s find it quickly
Pick up Golden Bulala
Golden Bulala is here
You found Golden Bulala
But it seems a little different
Why doesn’t it shine?
Was it broken?
This is not Golden Bulala
So where is the real Golden Bulala?
You have found it
where
You will know gradually
It’s as if His Majesty didn’t say anything.
He’s always been like this, just get used to it
To be continued